

Grace Otuya

Nationality: Kenyan (+254) 703286262 **Date of birth:** 14/07/1998

Gender: Female **Email address:** gracenyangayi@gmail.com

Website: https://otuyanyangayi.github.io/my-portfolio/

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/grace-otuya/

• Address: kienjeku road kienjeku road, 00100 Nairobi (Kenya)

ABOUT ME

I am a BSc. Computer Science graduate with knowledge in Linux, html5, CSS, JavaScript and Microsoft systems. I have experience in computer networks, web conference systems and ICT systems support. I intend to grow my ICT skills as well as to learn various other attributes that will enhance my career growth and the growth of the organization in which I get the opportunity to work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Laravel Developer (remote)

eMerge student management system [09/12/2021 - 30/06/2022]

City: Melbourne Country: Australia

- System Testing and Maintenance
- User Support
- Debugging
- System modifications

ICT Attache

Kenya Forest Service [01/10/2020 - 31/12/2020]

City: Nairobi **Country:** Kenya

- Network Maintenance and Support (Router configuration)
- User Support
- System Testing and Maintenance
- Hardware Repair and Maintenance
- Computer Basic Skills

Data Collection Officer

KALRO [01/06/2021 - 30/06/2021]

City: Kakamega Country: Kenya

Collecting data from farmers in the county for policy making

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

St Pauls University [01/09/2017 – 19/11/2021]

Address: Kabuku, Kiambu county, Private Bag Limuru (Kenya)

https://www.spu.ac.ke/new/

Cisco Certified Network Associate

AFRALTI [15/02/2021 - 06/10/2021]

Address: Waiyaki way, Nairobi, 58902 – 00200 City Square (Kenya)

https://www.afralti.org/

Introduction To Cyber Security

Cisco Networking Academy [01/05/2021 – 01/06/2021]

Address: Online kienjeku road, online Nairobi (Kenya)

https://www.afralti.org/

Software Development

Moringa School [23/05/2022 – Current]

Address: Ngong Road, Nairobi kienjeku road, 00100 Nairobi (Kenya)

https://moringaschool.com/

KCSE CERTIFICATE

Booker Academy [18/01/2013 - 30/11/2016]

Address: Mumias, Kakamega, Private Bag Mumias (Kenya)

https://www.booker-academy.sc.ke/

PROJECTS

Dictionary Application

[21/07/2022 - 29/07/2022]

This is a simple React JavaScript application that allows the user to search for words and the get the meanings. It also

includes the words pronunciation, synonyms and antonyms. This application fetches data from a public API and uses CSS,

material-ui, bootstrap and font awesome for styling

https://otuyanyangayi.github.io/DictionaryApp/

Food Recipe Application

[21/06/2022 - 29/06/2022]

This is a vanilla JavaScript application with CSS and html that allows the user to search for foods and get the recipes. This

application fetches data from a public API.

https://otuyanyangayi.github.io/Food-recipes/

M Personal Portfolio

[05/06/2022 - 10/06/2022]

This application was built with vanilla JavaScript with CSS and html. It is my personal portfolio.

https://otuyanyangayi.github.io/my-portfolio/

Fitness By Otuya

[05/09/2022 - 10/09/2022]

This is a full stack fitness application that allows the user to keep track of their routines and meals.

https://fitnessbyotuya.vercel.app/